https://www.aceworldcompanies.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Who we are:
ACE World Companies is a manufacturer of American-made, custom designed material handling solutions. Our vast range of products, overhead cranes, wire rope hoists, end trucks and transfer cars both standard and custom, have been developed using the most sophisticated technologies available today.  Our website address is: https://www.aceworldcompanies.com.
What Data We Collect:
This site collects various types of information such as:
Voluntarily provided info such as name, company name, phone number and email address which is used to contact you when you fill out a quote form or a contact us form.  Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking and server logs. This site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of contact or quote forms.  It is the intent of Ace World Companies website to use this personal information for the sole purpose for which it was requested.
Use of Data Collected:
Ace World Companies may collect and use the personal information to assist us in the operation of our website and to answer the questions you had on the Contact Us Form or the Request a Quote form.  Ace World Companies does not nor will it ever sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists or names to third parties.
Cookies:
We do use cookies (cookies are the small files that a site or its service provider transfers to our computer hard drive through you web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.
We use cookies to help compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences  and tools in the future.
Opt-Out or Unsubscribe:
All users and visitors to our website may discontinue receiving communication from us by emailing us that you wish to unsubscribe.  Please send all email to sales@aceworldcompanies.com to unsubscribe from future communication.  For third party websites you must go to their website to unsubscribe.
Embedded Content From Other Websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Links To Other Websites:
Our website does contain links to other websites.  Ace World Companies does not claim or accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and or procedures of such websites.  We encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and read the privacy policy of other websites.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:
We are in compliance with the requirement of COPPA, we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age.  Our products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years or older.
How We Protect Your Data:
Ace World Companies shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities as to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of personal data in our control.
We also use SSL for authentication and private communications in an effort to build our users trust and confidence in the internet and website.
Acceptance of Terms:
By using this website you are accepting the terms and conditions within our privacy policy agreement.  Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted to this page.  If you do not agree with our terms or conditions you should refrain from using our website.  Your continued use of our website means that you are in agreement with our terms and conditions.
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.
